# Segun Abisagbo

Software Engineer. Strong in design, software architecture and problem-solving skills. Expert in Javascript, PHP, database analysis & design. Comfortable with DevOps. Full-stack developer. Focused on building pleasant experiences for the software user. Fast learner. Team player. Strong written and verbal communication skills.

https://github.com/segebee https://linkedin.com/in/segebee segebee@gmail.com (234) 812 174 7250 segebee@gmail.com Lagos, Nigeria.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Turing.com** — Senior Fullstack Engineer (FE-Heavy)

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Building javascript web applications for Turing's clients (US Startups) using React. Built highly performant/optimized dashboards/portals with authentication, AWS/Amplify/S3 integrations, web services integrations, mapping, PWAs etc

### **Interswitch** — Senior Software Consultant

OCTOBER 2019 - JANUARY 2021

Building web applications for Interswitch's Quickteller platform using the latest technologies like Docker, Kubernetes, React, Redux, Typescript. Building custom components. Using Hooks, Suspense, Portals and latest React tooling.

## **Telios Software Solutions,** Remote (UK) — Senior Software Engineer

JANUARY 2017 - JULY 2019

Building web and mobile apps for clients using React, React Native, GraphQL, Apollo, Relay. AWS DevOps; working with clusters, docker, deploying applications, S3, RDS, CloudFront, Autoscaling.

## **GetMobile Technologies,** Lagos, Nigeria — *Software Engineer*

JUNE 2014 - DECEMBER 2016

Led a brilliant team of software engineers who built Nigeria's first self serving health insurance platform for Avon HMO. Deployed SharePoint applications, integrated a government portal to Oracle BI and Siebel. Helped a government agency automate their accreditation system and go paperless. Deployed websites and mobile applications for clients

## Silicon Harbor, Lagos, Nigeria — Software Developer

MAY 2011 - APRIL 2014

Built software applications such as Facebook Apps, Blackberry apps, Government & Business applications, Traffic application, multi-vendor e-commerce application, paypal like payment portal, logistics platform.

#### **SKILLS**

Javascript: React, React Native, GraphQL, Apollo, Relay, NodeJS, MongoDB, PHP, Ionic, Angular, FireBase,

**PHP:** Laravel, CodeIgniter, Wordpress Development

Enterprise: Oracle Database, Oracle BI/Siebel (API Integration), SharePoint, SharePoint Online

Others: Java (Android), Testing, AWS, DevOps, Docker, App Store deployment

#### **VOLUNTEERING**

**Team Lead, Safetee**Building software to reduce sexual and domestic violence in Nigeria

**Google Developer Groups** mentoring.

#### **PROJECTS**

**Safetee** 

ScreenSaver JS

Pipedrive People Manager

**CSV SEARCH** 

**InstagramClone** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Lagos**, Lagos — *MGIS*

JUNE 2016 - JUNE 2018

Masters in Geographic Information Systems (In View).

## **Olabisi Onabanjo University**, Ogun, Nigeria — B. sc.

JUNE 2005 - JULY 2011

Bachelor's Degree In Urban and Regional Planning.

## NIIT, Lagos, Nigeria — Oracle Database Administrator.

AUGUST 2010 - SEPTEMBER 2011

OCA and OCP from Oracle University.